<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EezyGuest</string>
    <string name="mapbox_access_token"></string>


    <string name="privacypolicy">We value your trust and are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is meant to explain, in plain language (with a little bit of “blah blah” so the lawyers are happy), that: we don’t collect your personal data, we don’t track you, we don’t sell your information, and you are fully in control of whatever you store in our app.

        1. What We Collect:

        Absolutely Nothing.
        Neither the developers, nor the app itself, collect, harvest, or sell your personal data.

        We don’t ask for your location unless the feature you choose literally needs it (and even then, it stays with you).

        We don’t track your browsing, your clicks, your device ID, or anything else.

        2. Who Owns the Data?

        You do. Everything you put into the app, whether it’s your account details, posts, rooms, bookings, or whatever else, is yours.

        The app saves data in a database only for functionality (so you can log in again, view rooms, keep your history, etc.). That database is purely for running the service, not for spying.

        At no point do the developers take, copy, or redistribute your information.

        3. What About Servers and Databases?

        Data stored in the app’s database is tied to your account, so you can retrieve it later.

        The database is not mined for marketing, advertising, or analytics.

        No third party is given access.

        Once again: blah blah, you’re in charge.

        4. Third-Party Services

        If the app uses external services (like Firebase, Google Sign-In, or Payment Gateways), those services have their own privacy policies.

        We do not control how those services handle data, but we do not pass them anything extra beyond what’s strictly required for the app to function.

        5. Security

        We take reasonable steps to protect whatever is stored.

        But as with all online systems, no database is 100% unhackable. By using the app, you acknowledge that risk.

        That said, since we don’t collect or sell your info, there’s not much to “steal” anyway.

        6. Your Choices and Control

        You can add, edit, or delete your information anytime through the app.

        If you delete your account, all associated data is wiped.

        We don’t keep hidden backups of your personal data.

        7. Children’s Privacy

        This app is not designed to knowingly collect any data from children under the age of 13.

        Again, since we don’t collect data at all, this shouldn’t be an issue, but legal text requires us to say it.

        8. Changes to this Policy

        If we ever update this Privacy Policy, we’ll notify you inside the app.

        But remember: our core principle will never change — your data is yours, not ours.</string>


    <string-array name="predefined_values">
        <item>Anantnag</item>
        <item>Bandipora</item>
        <item>Baramulla</item>
        <item>Budgam</item>
        <item>Ganderbal</item>
        <item>Kulgam</item>
        <item>Kupwara</item>
        <item>Pulwama</item>
        <item>Shopian</item>
        <item>Srinagar</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="nav_open_drawer">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_close_drawer">Close navigation drawer</string>
</resources>